[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which medieval monument is an essential part of the archaeological sites of the Greek island Rhodes?", "correct_answer": "The Palace of the Grand Master", "incorrect_answers": ["The White Tower", "The Venice Castle of Naoussa", "The Odeon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Mrs. Murphys best friend in the Rita Mae Brown series?", "correct_answer": "Tucker Tee", "incorrect_answers": ["Puce", "Pinky", "Kahula"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How often can a healthy adult donate blood?", "correct_answer": "every 8 weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["every 6 weeks", "every 3 months", "every 6 months"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A twin fetus which does not develop during pregnancy is called this.", "correct_answer": "Vanishing twin", "incorrect_answers": ["Conjoined twin", "Multiple twin", "Fraternal twin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these characters gets killed in the movie Romeo Must Die?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Colin ODay", "Po Sing", "Silk"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What should cows be fed on to produce the milk used for the making of Cantal cheese?", "correct_answer": "Hay", "incorrect_answers": ["Grass", "Grains", "Whey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest commercial city of Libya?", "correct_answer": "Tripoli", "incorrect_answers": ["Ethiopia", "Windhoek", "Nouakchott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie tells the story of a former U.S. Marine who becomes a teacher nicknamed white bread by her minority students.", "correct_answer": "Dangerous Minds", "incorrect_answers": ["Finding Forrester", "Dangerous Liaisons", "Freedom Writers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it just a myth that the fireplace in the background, during the Black Knight scene of Monty Python and the Holy Grail, goes out and comes on as the camera shots change?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Vito Corleone die in the 1972 gangster movie The Godfather?", "correct_answer": "He dies of a heart attack.", "incorrect_answers": ["In an accident", "He is killed.", "He commits suicide."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Poseidon Adventure, what was the profession of Linda before she married detective Rogo?", "correct_answer": "prostitute", "incorrect_answers": ["barmaid", "policewoman", "hair dresser"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The fruit of most olive species contain phenolic compounds and oleuropein which make the fruit too bitter. However, the fruit of this olive cultivar can be eaten fresh.", "correct_answer": "Thassos Olive", "incorrect_answers": ["Manzanilla", "Bosana", "Arbequina"]}]